A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25 (A99) FA477
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A99), 1974-1999; 1.25; 99.6 Cubic Feet; 83 standard record storage cartons. Boxes R3191-R3252, R3266-R3286.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 94034 A 448 - SHANGHAI MEDICAL UNIVERSITY- CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY/HEALTH ECONOMICS STUDY, 1992-1997 (Box R3242)
    - RF 94035 A 21 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - NEEDS-BASED HEALTH REFORM WORKSHOP, 1994-1997 (Box R3242)
    - RF 94035 A 29 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - THIRD MEETING OF NETWORK OF AFRICAN POSTGRADUATE TRAINING AND RESEARCH INSTITUTIONS IN PUBLIC HEALTH IN CONGO, 1995-1997 (Box R3242)
    - 940036 - HEALTH SCIENCE FOR THE TROPICS, 1986-1998; 6 folders of project records and 5 supplementary material folders spanning boxes R2342, R2343 and R2344. (Box R3242)
    - 940036 - HEALTH SCIENCE FOR THE TROPICS, 1986-1998; 6 folders of project records and 5 supplementary material folders spanning boxes R2342, R2343 and R2344. (Box R3243)
    - 940036 - HEALTH SCIENCE FOR THE TROPICS, 1986-1998; 6 folders of project records and 5 supplementary material folders spanning boxes R2342, R2343 and R2344. (Box R3244)
    - RF 94039 A 9 - JERUSALEM INTERNATIONAL BOOK FAIR - PARTICIPATIOIN OF AUTHORS AND PUBLISHERS FROM ARABIC SPEAKING COUNTRIES AT BOOK FAIR, 1994-1995 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94039 A 12 - SANART: ASSOCIATION FOR THE PROMOTION OF VISUAL ARTS IN TURKEY, 1994-1997 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94039 A 13 - CENTER FOR PALESTINE RESEARCH AND STUDIES (ISRAEL) - POLLS AND SURVEYS IN WEST BANK, GAZA AND JERUSALEM, 1994-1996 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94039 A 13 - CENTER FOR PALESTINE RESEARCH AND STUDIES (ISRAEL) - POLLS AND SURVEYS IN WEST BANK, GAZA AND JERUSALEM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3245)
    - RF 94039 A 14 - TURKISH ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL STUDIES FOUNDATION (TURKEY} - WORKSHOP ON ROLL OF THINK TANKS AND RESEARCH CENTERS IN MUSLIM SOCIETIES, 1995-1997 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94043 A 207 - IHU - EDITORA A PRODUCOES ARTISTICAS (BRAZIL) - A CELEBRATION OF INDIGENOUS AMAZON MUSIC, 1994-1998 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94048 A 1 - AMERICAN CIVIL LIBERTIES UNION FOUNDATION - REDISTRICTING CHALLENGES UNDER THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT, 1994-1996 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94048 A 2 - SOUTHERN REGIONAL COUNCIL - REDISTRICTING AND MINORITIES (ELECTORAL PARTICIPATION PROJECT), 1990-1997; 2 folders. (Box R3245)
    - RF 94048 A3 - LAWYERS' COMMITTEE FOR CIVIL RIGHTS UNDER LAW - REDISTRICTING UNDER THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT, 1994-1996 (Box R3245)
    - RF 94048 A 4 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND - REDISTRICTING UNDER THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT, 1993-1996 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94049 A 199 - INTERNATIONAL FILM SEMINARS - 1995 ROBERT FLAHERTY SEMINAR, 1995-1996 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94050 A 2 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - PUBLICATIONS ON AGROECOLOGY, 1994, 1998 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94055 A 11 - SPENCER MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATES - SOLAR COMBINED CYCLE SYSTEM IN MEXICO, 1993-1997 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94056 A 73 - FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION - DONORS WORKING GROUP 1995 PARIS MEETING, 1995, 1999 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94060 A 6 - VISIONS OF A BETTER WORLD FOUNDATION USA - LINKAGES BETWEEN CITIZENS AND THEIR GOVERNMENTS, 1995-1998 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94061 A 81 - MEXICAN FINE ARTS CENTER- 1995 SOR JUANA DE LA CRUZ FESTIVAL, 1995-1997 (Box R3246)
    - RF 94065 - TOMAS RIVERA CENTER - NEEDS OF HISPANICS, 1987-1998; 6 folders in total - stored in 2 boxes - Box R3246 and Box R3247. Three folders of project/grant records, and 3 folders of supplementary material. (Box R3246)
    - RF 94065 - TOMAS RIVERA CENTER - NEEDS OF HISPANICS, 1987-1998 (Box R3247)
    - RF 95001 A 323 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (IRRI) - RESEARCH TERMINAL SEQUENCING OF MAPPED RICE GENOMIC PROBES, 1992-1997 (Box R3247)
    - RF 95001 A 343 - INSTITUTE OF BIOTECHNOLOGY (VIETNAM) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR DINH THI PHONG, 1994-1996 (Box R3247)
    - RF 95001 A 361 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR SIRIWAN BURIKAM, 1995-1996 (Box R3247)
    - RF 95001 A 363 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR B. BALASUBRAMANIAN, 1994-1996 (Box R3247)
    - RF 95001 A 371 - UNIVERSITY OF DURHAM - BROWN PLANT HOPPER RESISTANCE, 1989-1996 (Box R3248)
    - RF 95001 A 387 - MAJARAJA SAYAJIRAO UNIVERSITY OF BARODA (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR VAISHALI J. PATEL, 1994-1995 (Box R3248)
    - RF 95003 A 561 - UNIVERSITY OF COLORADO - RESIDENT FELLOWS, 1991-1996 (Box R3248)
    - RF 95010 A 40 - POPULATION ACTION INTERNATIONAL POST-CAIRO PROGRAM INITIATIVE, 1995-1997 (Box R3248)
    - RF 95017 A 18 - INTERNATIONAL RESCUE COMMITTEE, INC. - BC CONFERENCE: UNACCOMPANIED REFUGEE MINORS, 1993-1995 (Box R3248)
    - RF 96034 A 112 - SOUTHERN AFRICA NETWORK OF AIDS SERVICE ORGANIZATIONS (ZIMBABWE) - CONFERENCE ON "AIDS AND SEXUALITY", 1994-1998 (Box R3248)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Background material, 1990-1991 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Terms of Reference 1991-93, 1991-1993 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Robert McNamara, 1991-1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Leading up to London Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Bellagio - Invites and Responses, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Bellagio, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Letters to Heads of State, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Chair Selection, 1992 (Box R3286)
      Restricted from scholarly access - personnel material.
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Paris, 1992 July 17 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Potential Members, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Maria Lourdes De Pintasilgo (Appointment Letters), 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Javier Perez de Cuellar, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Bellagio - Draft Agenda, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Preliminary Budget and Commission staffing, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Sensitive Material, 1991-1992 (Box R3286)
      Restricted from scholarly access.
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Meeting at Rockefeller Foundation, 1993 July 22, 1992-1994 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - UNESCO Agreement, 1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Pintasilgo, 1992-1993 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Senarclens, 1992-1993 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Donors and Staffing, 1992-1993 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - London - Thank-you's/Term of Reference, 1991-1992 (Box R3286)
    - RF 92036 - Independent Commission on Population - Supplementary - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box R3286)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - AS 9147 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - CHINESE STUDENT ASSOCIATION JOURNAL PUBLICATION, 1989-1996 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9247 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - TRAINING DEVELOPING COUNTRY SCIENTISTS IN DNA MARKER TECHNOLOGY IN VIGNA, 1992-1996 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9302 - CHIANG MAl UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - TEA GARDENS PROJECT, 1992-1997 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9305 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - FOCUSING AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH ON SMALL SCALE FARMERS NEEDS, 1992-1997 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9317 - MANILA OBSERVATORY - COMMUNITY FOREST LAND MANAGEMENT ANALYSIS PROJECT, 1992-1996 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9318 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - NATURAL REGENERATION AND NON-WOOD FOREST PRODUCTS, 1993-1995 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9321 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MEETING ON FOOD AND POPULATION TRENDS OVER NEXT TWENTY YEARS, 1992-1994 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9321 - INTERNATIONAL FOOD POLICY RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MEETING ON FOOD AND POPULATION TRENDS OVER NEXT TWENTY YEARS - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3266)
    - AS 9328 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA - PLANNING COMMITTEE TO INCREASE AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTIVITY, 1993-1997 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9332 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - SYMPOSIUM IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE XV INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS OF SOIL SCIENCE, 1992-1993, 1997 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9334 - SENGOOBA, T., 1990-1995 (Box R3266)
    - AS 9401 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (DAVIS) - SEMINAR SERIES ON INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE, 1993-1996 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9407 - AFRICAN CENTRE FOR TECHNOLOGY STUDIES (KENYA)- BOOK, MORE PEOPLE, LESS EROSION, 1994-1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9408 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (CIAT) (COLOMBIA) - MEETING OF THE RESEARCH CONSORTIUM FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF ACID SOILS, 1994, 1997 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-12 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME {KENYA) - ATTENDANCE OF MARY OKWAKOL AT THE FIRST GLOBAL CHANGE AND TERRESTRIAL ECOSYSTEMS SCIENCE CONFERENCE, 1994-1995 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-19 - STRENGTHENING FOOD PRODUCTION SYSTEMS IN AFRICA - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE TO CONSULTATIVE GROUP ON INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (CGIAR) FOR LIVESTOCK RESEARCH, 1993-1998 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-22 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - SECOND CROP SCIENCE CONFERENCE FOR EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA; AFRICAN CROP SCIENCE JOURNAL, 1993-1997 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-23 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH CENTRE - INTEGRATED PEST MANAGEMENT TRAINING FOR AN ENTOMOLOGIST, 1994, 1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9505 - UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA (GAINESVILLE) - NITROGEN USE EFFICIENCY OF MAIZE, 1995-1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9517 - PAREJA, MARIO R. - PESTS AND DISEASES OF MAIZE IN SOUTHEASTERN MEXICO, 1995-1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9531 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENTIFIC AND INDUSTRIAL RESEARCH ORGANIZATION (AUSTRALIA) - WORKSHOP ON MOLECULAR BIOLOGY, 1995-1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9533 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - CONFLICT RESOLUTION IN FOREST RESOURCE MANAGEMENT, 1995, 1998 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-24 - RENE DUBOS CENTER FOR HUMAN ENVIRONMENTS, INC.- BC CONFERENCE: TECHNOLOGICAL PROSPECTS FOR SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE, 1993-1997 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-27 - UNIVERSIDAD DE BUENOS AIRES (ARGENTINA) - GRADUATE COURSE ON SUSTAINABILITY OF NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT, 1994-1995 (Box R3267)
    - 94-8100-28 - SUSTAINABLE SOILS MANAGEMENT - PARTICIPATION AT CIMMYT'S INTERNATIONAL INSECT RESISTANT MAIZE SYMPOSIUM OF RF-FUNDED SCIENTISTS WORKING IN AFRICA AND MEXICO, 1994, 1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9432 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - SOIL SCIENCE SOCIETY OF EAST AFRICA - 14TH CONFERENCE, 1994-1995 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9435 - COLEGIO DE POSTGRADUADOS (MEXICO) - MAIZE-LEGUME SYSTEMS IN THE STATE OF CHIAPAS, 1994, 1997 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9439 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - MILPA SOIL FERTILITY AND PRODUCTIVITY IN THE YUCATAN PENINSULA, 1994-1996 (Box R3267)
    - AS 9503 - MALAWI- RELIEF AND REHABILITATION AFFAIRS (MINISTRY OF) - SEMINAR ON AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION AND FOOD SECURITY, 1994-1997 (Box R3267)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 9232 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - LATINO URBAN POLICY INITIATIVE, 1990-1996, 1999 (Box R3268)
    - EO 9232 - UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN - ENTREPRENEURIAL EXPERIENCE IN THE U.S. STUDY, 1993-1996 (Box R3268)
    - EO 9315 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - GED AND LABOR MARKET PROSPECTS FOR HIGH SCHOOL DROPOUTS, 1993-1995 (Box R3268)
    - EO 9322 - MANPOWER RESEARCH DEMONSTRATION CORP. - FIRST PHASE EVALUATION OF CAREER ACADEMIES, 1993-1997 (Box R3268)
    - EO 9402 - CHILDREN NOW, 1988-1995; 3 folders. (Box R3269)
    - EO 9402 - CHILDREN NOW - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 3 folders. (Box R3270)
    - EO 9403 - MOREHOUSE COLLEGE - RESEARCH INSTITUTE, 1989-1995 (Box R3270)
    - 94-8020-5 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - JOB OPPORTUNITIES IN PUBLIC HOUSING DEMONSTRATION, 1993-1995 (Box R3270)
    - 94-8020-7 - NATIONAL CONGRESS FOR COMMUNITY ECONOMIC DEVELOMENT - THIRD NATIONAL COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT SURVEY, 1993-1996 (Box R3270)
    - 94-8020-8 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - INNER-CITY YOUTH IN THE LOW-WAGE SERVICE SECTOR, 1992-1996 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-9 - MEMPHIS STATE UNIVERSITY - MEASURE EFFECTS OF SOCIAL INTERVENTIONS, 1994-1996 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-10 - DEVELOPMENT FUND - COMMUNITY ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT LENDING INITIATIVE'S GENERAL SUPPORT, 1993-1996 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-11 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - BOOK "CHANGING POVERTY/CHANGING JOBS", 1994-1996 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-12 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - "A POLICY STUDY GROUP FOR COMMUNITY BASED DEVELOPMENT", 1994-1997 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-14 - WORK FOR WISCONSIN (WFW) - COMMUNITY SERVICE JOBS DESIGN PROJECT, 1994-1995 (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-14 - WORK FOR WISCONSIN (WFW) - COMMUNITY SERVICE JOBS DESIGN PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Box R3271)
    - 94-8020-16 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN (MADISON) - SUSTAINABLE MILWAUKEE PROJECT, 1993-1996 (Box R3272)
    - EO 9419 - FAMILY SERVICE AMERICA - POLICY AND SERVICE DELIVERY AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATIONS, 1994-1997 (Box R3272)
  - Global Environment (GE)
    - GE 9031 - COMMITTEE OF SOVIET SCIENTISTS - 21ST CENTURY LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1990-1992 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9110 - ORANGI PILOT PROJECT - COMMUNITY-MANAGED SANITATION, 1991-1995 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9113 - INTERNATIONAL SOCIAL SCIENCE COUNCIL - CAPACITY INCREASE, 1990-1996 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9119 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - JUTE BIODEGRADABLE PRODUCTS, 1991-1993, 1998 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9130 - UNIVERSITY OF TENNESSEE - BIOMASS-TO-ELECTRICITY PROJECT IN CHINA, 1991-1998 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9205 - PEOPLE'S GOVERNMENT OF HAINAN PROVINCE - 1992-1993 MEETINGS OF THE INTERNATIONAL ADVISORY COUNCIL (IAC), 1992-1994 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9216 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENCE COUNCIL - NATURAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box R3272)
    - GE9218 - ASIA NETWORK FOR SMALL SCALE AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGIES (ANSAB) - STUDY MICROPROPAGATION OF THE KAPOK TREE IN JAVA, 1992-1996 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9219 - FOOD AND AGRICULTURAL ORGANIZATION OF THE UNITED NATIONS (FAO) - INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON JUTE AND ENVIRONMENT, 1992-1994, 1998 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9221 - COMMONWEALTH SCIENCE COUNCIL - BIOMASS '93 CONFERENCE, 1992-1994 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9301 - INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL ECONOMICS - "TRADE, DEVELOPMENT AND THE ENVIRONMENT: NEW LINKAGES AND CHALLENGES", 1992-1994 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9302 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC CONFERENCE: ENERGY STRATEGIES FOR THE 21ST CENTURY, 1992-1993, 1996 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9303 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - PARTICIPATION OF DEVELOPING COUNTRY SCIENTISTS AT WORKSHOP, 1993 (Box R3272)
    - GE 9308 - CONSERVATION LAW FOUNDATION - ENERGY EFFICIENCY PROGRAM IN JAMAICA, 1990-1993 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9309 - ENERGY GLOBAL DE COSTA RICA, S.A. - ENERGY EFFICIENCY PROJECT, 1993-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9310 - ENVIRONMENTAL ENTERPRISES ASSISTANCE FUND - RENEWABLE ENERGY DEVELOPMENT, 1991-1996 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9313 - UNIVERSITY OF SAO PAULO (BRAZIL) - GRADUATE PROGRAM ON ENERGY, 1991-1994, 1998 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9314 - ENERGIA GLOBAL, INC. - PRE-CONSTRUCTION PHASE DON PEDRO HYDROELECTRIC IN COSTA RICA, 1993-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9315 - BARGHINI, ALESSANDRO - INCREASING USE OF EFFICIENT ELECTRICITY IN GALAPAGOS ISLANDS, 1993-1994 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9316 - SPENCER MANAGEMENT ASSOCIATES - USE OF PARABOLIC TROUGH SOLAR ELECTRIC GENERATING STATIONS, 1993-1994 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9317 - BIOMASS USERS NETWORK (BUN) - USING PLANT OIL FOR ELECTRICITY GENERATION IN BRAZIL, 1993, 1998-1999 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9402 - INTERNATIONAL ENERGY INITIATIVE - BIORESOURCES '94 CONFERENCE, 1993-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9403 - STOCKHOLM ENVIRONMENT INSTITUTE (SEI) (SWEDEN) - POLESTAR PROJECT, 1993-1996, 1999 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9404 - ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION ADMINISTRATION (CHINA) - TAIPEI MEETING ON AEDES AEGYPTI/DENGUE CONTROL, 1992-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9405 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA- CHINA'S RURAL ENERGY CONSTRUCTION PROGRAM, 1993-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9408 - BRASCEP ENGENHARIA LTDA. (BRAZIL) - POWER GENERATION AT JALLES MACHADO SUGAR PLANT, 1994-1995 (Box R3273)
    - GE 9409 - CENTER FOR CLEAN AIR POLICY - REPLICABLE STRUCTURE FOR ENERGY PROJECT, 1994-1995, 1999 (Box R3273)
    - 94-8130-13 - ONTARIO HYDRO (CANADA) - GLOBAL ENERGY EFFICIENCY COLLABORATIVE MEETING, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box R3274)
    - 94-8130-14 - FUTURE DIRECTIONS FOR THE UNITED NATIONS ENVIRONMENT PROGRAMME - BC CONFERENCE, 1994, 1998 (Box R3274)
    - 94-8130-16 - CONFERENCE OF THE BELLAGIO FORUM FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT- LISBON CONFERENCE, 1993-1994 (Box R3274)
    - GE 9417 - INSTITUTO NACIONAL DE BIODIVERSIDAD (COSTA RICA) - FEASIBILITY STUDY FOR CENTRAL AMERICAN-MANAGED INSTITUTION TO SUPPORT SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 1994-1996 (Box R3274)
    - GE 9418 - GREENS UNION OF ARMENIA - DESIGN OF BIOGAS PLANT IN ARMENIA, 1994-1997 (Box R3274)
    - GE 9419 - CENTER FOR CLEAN AIR POLICY - COSTA RICAN-U.S. CLIMATE CHANGE PROJECT, 1994-1995 (Box R3274)
    - GE 9420 - CONFERENCE OF THE BELLAGION FORUM FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT - FIRST ANNUAL CONFERENCE IN LONDON, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box R3274)
    - GE 9502 - EARTH COUNCIL (COSTA RICA) - BERLIN CLIMATE CHANGE MEETING, 1995-1997 (Box R3274)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - HS 9048 - CENTER FOR DISEASE CONTROL - VARIOLA VIRUS SEQUENCE STRAINS, 1990-1995 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9112 - MOl UNIVERSITY - MATERNAL AND CHILD HEALTH, 1987-1994 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9144 - AMERICAN SOCIETY OF TROPICAL MEDICINE AND HYGIENE - XIII INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS FOR TROPICAL MEDICINE AND MALARIA, 1991-1992, 1996-1999 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9208 - ACHESON, ROY, 1989-1994, 1997-1998 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9216 - MOI UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - MEDICAL FACULTY PRACTICE PROGRAM, 1991-1994, 1998 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9225 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL AND DEVELOPMENT - IMPACT OF ANTIBODY ENHANCEMENT OF RSV INFECTION ON IMMUNE RESPONSE, 1991-1997 (Box R3274)
    - HS 9231 - FOUNDATION FOR INTERNATIONAL SCIENTIFIC COOPERATION, 1986-1993, 1996-1998 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9239 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - MALARIA FORUM, 1992-1996 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9240 - WALTER REED ARMY MEDICAL CENTER - VIROLOGY IN THAILAND, 1989-1993, 1996-1997 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9247 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - "CURRICULUM DEVELOPMENT: EXPERIENCE OF ZAIRE SCHOOL OF PUBLIC HEALTH", 1991-1997 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9307 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - COMPARATIVE ETHNOGRAPHIC STUDIES IN HEALTH/MENTAL HEALTH IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1993-1996 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9309 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH (PATH) - EPSTEIN-BARR VIRUS VACCINE TASL FORCE, 1991-1996 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9319 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - INTERDISCIPLINARY INITIATIVE IN ENVIRONMENT, DEVELOPMENT AND HEALTH, 1993-1994 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9327 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA PRESS - BOOK ON HEPATITIS B IMMUNIZATION, 1993-1996 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9404 - CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - PRODUCING VACCINES FOR DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1993-1995 (Box R3275)
    - HS 9406 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - 1994 FORUM AND BELLAGIO CONFERENCE ON "LEADERSHIP IN HEALTH FOR THE 21ST CENTURY", 1993-1995 (Box R3275)
    - 94-8110-8 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - BIOGRAPHICAL DOCUMENTARY VIDEO ON PUBLIC HEALTH IN INDIA, 1993-1998 (Box R3275)
    - 94-8110-10 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - LEISHMANIASIS AND NORTHEASTERN BRAZIL, 1988-1997 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-11 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - PURCHASE AND DISTRIBUTION COSTS OF PARASITIC DISEASES IN WATER RESOURCES DEVELOPMENT, 1994 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-12 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - 1994 GENEVA MEETING ON URBAN HEALTH, 1994-1997 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-14 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY- INTERNATIONAL MENTAL AND BEHAVIORAL HEALTH, 1991-1996 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-15 - INSTITUTE FOR HEALTHCARE IMPROVEMENT - IMPROVE HEALTH CARE SYSTEMS OF DEVELOPING WORLD, 1993-1995 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-18 - SATELLIFE - AFRICAN COMMUNICATIONS NETWORK, 1989-1995, 1998 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-19 - TIDES FOUNDATION - CHOLERA PREVENTION USING WATER PURIFICATION SYSTEMS, 1994 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-20 - UNIVERSITY OF CALABAR - STUDY TREATMENT AND CONTROL OF URINARY SCHISTOSOMIASIS IN CHILDREN, 1992-1996 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-24 - UNIVERSITY OF CEARA - LEISHMANIASIS AND NORTHEASTERN BRAZIL, 1988-1996 (Box R3276)
    - 94-8110-26 - ASIAN GROUP FOR RAPID VIRAL DIAGNOSIS (SINGAPORE) - THIRD ASIA-PACIFIC CONGRESS OF MEDICAL VIROLOGY, 1993-1997 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9427 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - ENABLE RESEARCHER TO PARTICIPATE IN TAKEMI PROGRAM IN INTERNATIONAL HEALTH, 1994-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9433 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - CONTEMPORARY ISSUES IN MATERNAL HEALTH CARE IN AFRICA, 1993-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9434 - COMMONWEALTH MEDICAL ASSOCIATION (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP ON ADOLESCENT HEALTH IN CAPE TOWN, 1994-1995 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9436 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - DATA ANALYSIS OF ANTHROPOLOGIC STUDY IN PHILIPPINES, 1994-1997 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9437 - COMCARE INTERNATIONAL, INC. - SOLAR-POWERED HEATING AID, 1994-1995 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9439 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - CENTER FOR POPULATION AND FAMILY HEALTH - DATABASE CENTER ON FEMALE GENITAL MUTILATION, 1994-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9441 - INTERNATIONAL PROJECTS ASSISTANCE SERVICES - POST-ABORTION SERVICES IN ZIMBABWE, 1993-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9443 - UGANDA VIRUS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BROAD SPECTRUM ANTIMICROBIAL THERAPY ON VAGINAL FLORA, 1994-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9444 - UGANDA VIRUS RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MATERNAL AND INFANT HEALTH, 1994-1996 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9501 - CHRISTIAN MEDICAL COLLEGE AND HOSPITAL (INDIA) - CONFERENCE ON ROLE OF UNIVERSITY IN HEALTH RESEARCH, 1994-1995 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9505 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - REVIEW GLOBAL PROGRAM FOR VACCINES, 1994-1997 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9515 - WOODALL, JOHN P. - MEETING ON EMERGING INFECTIOUS DISEASES IN GERMANY, 1995 (Box R3277)
    - HS 9517 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - 1995 INTERNATIONAL HEALTH LEADERSHIP FORUM, 1995-1996 (Box R3277)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - PS 9042 - POPULATION COUNCIL, INC.- PROGESTERONE INHIBITOR AND FERTILITY, 1990-1995 (Box R3277)
    - PS 9225 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - WILLIAM H. DRAPER, JR., FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 1992-1996, 1999 (Box R3277)
    - PS 9245 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - BIRTH INTERVAL LENGTH DYNAMICS IN RURAL WEST AFRICA, 1990-1995 (Box R3277)
    - PS 9251 - JSI RESEARCH AND TRAINING INSTITUTE INC. - FAMILY PLANNING SECTOR PROGRAMME: INTERNSHIPS FOR KENYAN GRADUATES, 1992-1994 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9305 - AMERICAN COLLEGE OF OBSTETRICIANS AND GYNECOLOGISTS - NATIONAL ADVISORY BOARD ON ETHICS IN REPRODUCTION, 1992-1994, 1997 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9326 - UNIVERSITY OF CHILE - EFFECTS OF ENDOMETRIAL & TUBAL FLUIDS ON THE PROCESS OF CAPACITATION OF HUMAN SPERMATOZOA, 1992-1998 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9341 - PATHFINDER INTERNATIONAL - UNSAFE ABORTION IN ADDIS ABABA AND NAIROBI, 1992-1997 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9401 - UNIVERSITY OF IOWA - STUDY C-KIT PROTONCOGENE, 1993-1996 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9412 - UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS (NIGERIA) - PUBLISH PAPERS FROM 1993 MEETING ON REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1993-1995, 1999 (Box R3278)
    - PS 9413 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH (PATH) - PUBLICATION, "OUTLOOK", 1993-1995 (Box R3278)